okay so let me tell you about a ramp up pentagon announces new international mission to counter
attacks on commercial vessels in red sea okay so yemen is a little country right here as you can
see israel is right there and if you want to get something to israel you're gonna have to go past
yemen now yemen said not so fast if you're messing with palestine you're messing with us now mind you
yemen got their own stuff going on they've got food shortages they've got health care shortages
they've been at it with their neighbor saudi arabia it's a real situation over there however
it's even been enhanced because they're actually creating more blockades based on yemen saying
nah y'all not gonna get on these palestinians now when we say yemen we mean the houthis a rebel group
supported by iran but they are yemeni and they have boarded ships and they have shut down anything
moving towards israel y'all when they said there's no oil going all of a sudden the brits were like
actually it quite like a ceasefire but you know how the u.s has ignored like the entire world asking
for a ceasefire the u.s has announced a 10 nation task force to protect shipping in the red sea
these reckless hoodie attacks are a serious international problem and they demand a firm
international response i just want to point out one he calls the attacks reckless the way these
people weaponize adjectives when they're literally very pointedly on ships and they've never said
anything like that about the carpet bombing happening in palestine two he's saying this is
an international issue what is a genocide well the issue about to be pitbull aka mr worldwide because
the houthis are backed by iran and they said y'all about to run and find out could this be the
world war we anticipated happening possibly